Guide to the AFSCME, Local 420, Hospital Workers Records WAG.215
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: President's Office Files, 1967-2001.
  - Butler, James: AFSCME Vice-Presidential Campaign, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Butler, James: Biographical, 1992-2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Butler, James: Speeches, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Butts, Reverend Calvin, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bylaws, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Campaign for a New South, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Carrillo, J. Emilio, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Carrillo, J. Emilio: Hazardous Waste Meeting, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Carrillo, J. Emilio: Resignation, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Carrion, Anthony, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Carter, James (Stabbing of), 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Carthan, Eddie (Mayor of Tchula, MS), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Centers for Disease Control: Grants, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Centers for Disease Control: Meeting-Blackwell and Tolliver Testimony, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Central Supply Assistants, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - CETA Workers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Chapter Chairs and Shop Stewards Lists, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Charles, Carmen, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Charter Change (NYC), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Church of God in Christ, Inc., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - City Hospital Visiting Committee Report, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - City Hospital Worker, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - City Hospital Worker: Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - City of Hope, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - City-wide Contracts, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - City-wide Equal Employment Opportunity Committee, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Civil Service Examination: Veterans' Preference, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Civil Rights: American Weekly Newspaper, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clarke, Lee, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clinton, Hillary, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, May 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Coalition for Community Empowerment of Greater Southeast Queens (formerly, People Against Crack), 1987 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 1979-1998 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - CBTU, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - CBTU Conference, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - CBTU Convention (Detroit), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - CBTU Convention (New Orleans), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - CBTU Dinner Dance, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - CBTU Political Action Seminar, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CBTU Tri-State Conference, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CBTU Tri-State Conference, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CBTU Women's Luncheon, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Commission on the Public's Health System, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Positive Youth, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Community Advisory Board, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Community Health Boards, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Community-Labor Coalition for Social and Economic Justice, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Community Service Council of Greater Harlem, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Comptroller's Report, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Coney Island Hospital, 1986-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Arbitration, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Cafeteria Privatization, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Cafeteria Privatization (Saunders v. HHC), 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Grievances, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Health and Safety, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Conference on the Harlem Recovery Plan, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Black Caucus Legislative Weekend, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Districts (NY): Union Strength, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Constitution (L420), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Contribution Limits, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Co-op City Baptist Church: Requests (re: Choir), 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Corporate Nursing Services, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Members, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cumberland Neighborhood Family Care Center (N.F.C.C.), 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cumberland N.F.C.C.: Layoffs, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cumberland N.F.C.C.: Rally, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cuomo, Governor Mario M.: Proposed Health Care Bill, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Daily Challenge: Giuliani v. Hospital Workers, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - DeBow, Louise, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Democratic National Convention, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Democratic Party, New York State, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Department of Corrections, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Department of Corrections, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Department of Corrections: Bronx House of Detention, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Department of Corrections: Dietary Aides, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Department of Corrections: Rikers Island-Safety and Health, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Diallo, Amadou, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Dietary Aides, 1980-1994 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Dissidents: Election Materials, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Dissidents: L-420 and Disputes with DC-37, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - District 1199 Strike, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - District Attorney's Office: Investigation, 1998, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Domestic Partners Benefits, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Dominican Republic: Trade Unions, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Dues, Undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Ebenezer Missionary Baptist Church, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Election: Chapter Chairs, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Elections: L-420, 1981-1987 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Elections: Nominations L-420, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Elections: Tallies, Rosters, Poll Watchers, Etc., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Elmhurst Hospital, 1987-2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Dietary Aides Complaints, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Employee Assistance Programs, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Labor-Management Meeting, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Spanish Unit, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - EMT Cadet Training, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Equity Panel Discussion (Compensation), 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ethiopia: Aid, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ethiopia: Concert, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Eve, Arthur O.: Honored, Mar 19, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1988-2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Expenses: Parties, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Expenses: Retirement, Etc., 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Federation of African-American Civil Service Organizations, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Federation of African-American Civil Service Organizations, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fee for Service Plans, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Finance/Political Action Committees, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Finances (L-420), 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - First Baptist Church, Brooklyn, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Flake, Floyd: Election, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Fordham Hospital, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Foster, Helen Diane, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Francis, Keith, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Frank, Andre: Shooting, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Frank, Wilma McCoy, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Frontier Hotel (Las Vegas, NV): Strike, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Fulani, Dr. Lenore, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Gaskins, Joseph: Funeral, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - General Membership Meetings, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Goins, Clyde, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Goldwater Hospital, 1985-1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Goldwater Hospital: AIDS Unit, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Goldwater Hospital: Parking Restrictions, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Gore Campaign, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Gotbaum, Victor, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gouverneur Hospital, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gouverneur Hospital: AIDS Assessment Center, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Gouverneur Hospital: Benejan Case, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Gouverneur Hospital: Per Diem Workers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gracie Mansion Vigil, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Greater Harlem Chapter (L-420), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Green, Mark, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Gulf War, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Gulf War: Protests, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Haiti: Solidarity March, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Harlem Dental Service, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Harlem Hospital, 1985-2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Harlem Hospital: Contracting Out Laundry, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Harlem Hospital: Crisis, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Harlem Hospital: Endowment Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Harlem Hospital: Housekeeping Aides, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Harlem Hospital: Inspection Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Harlem Hospital: IV Team, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Harlem Hospital: Lay-offs, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Harlem Hospital: Nursing Program, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Harlem Hospital: 100th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Harlem Hospital: Overtime Pay Problems, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Harlem Hospital: Protest, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Harlem Hospital: Protest, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Harlem Housing Tenant Association, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Hatch Act Reform Conference (AFSCME/AFGE), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Hawkins, Elder Awards Luncheon, Jun 10, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 1981-1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - HHC: Affirmative Action, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - HHC: Agreements, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - HHC: AIDS Employee Training, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - HHC: AIDS Task Force, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - HHC: Adams, Romero, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - HHC: Asbestos Abatement Program, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - HHC: Barondess Report, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - HHC: Board of Directors Meetings, 1989-1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - HHC: Broad Banding, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - HHC: Budget, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - HHC: Check Cashing Fees, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - HHC: Discrimination Issues, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - HHC: Educational Leave, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - HHC: Employees Suggestion Program, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - HHC: Fee for Service Plans, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - HHC: Finance Committee, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - HHC: Health and Safety, 1987, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - HHC: Hiring Practices, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - HHC: History, 1967-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - HHC: J. Emilio Carrillo, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - HHC: Job Descriptions, 1972-1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - HHC: Jones, Billy, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - HHC: Layoff Lists, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - HHC: Mayoral Advisory Panel Report, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - HHC: Meetings, 1986-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - HHC: Memos, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - HHC: Municipal Labor Coalition Committee, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - HHC: Municipal Labor Committee, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - HHC: Municipal Labor Committee Meetings, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - HHC: NYC Contract, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - HHC: NYC Council Testimony, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - HHC: Nursing, Restraint and Seclusion Policies, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - HHC: Nursing Supervision Protocol, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - HHC: Operating Procedure, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - HHC: Preferred List, 1991-1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - HHC: Report on Health Security Act, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - HHC: Regionalization Plan, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - HHC: Restraint/Seclusion Guidelines, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - HHC: Ribivarin Policy, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - HHC: Safety Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - HHC: Smoking, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - HHC: Structure, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - HHC: Training Contracts, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - HHC: Universal Precautions Procedure, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - HHC: Vacancy Reporting, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Health and Safety, 1986-1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Health and Safety: AFL-CIO Conference, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Health and Safety: Asbestos, 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Health and Safety: Avoiding Health Hazards, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Health and Safety: Carrillo Meeting, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Health and Safety: Dust, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Health and Safety: Ethylene Oxide Exposure, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Health and Safety: Hazardous Biological Waste, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Health and Safety: Latex Allergy, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Health and Safety: Mercury Exposure, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Health and Safety: Mortuary Care Technicians, Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Health and Safety: Needle Sticks, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Health and Safety: Pentamidine, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Health and Safety: Phlebotomy Procedures, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Health and Safety: "Right to Know" Handbooks, Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Health and Safety: Rikers Island, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Health and Safety: Tuberculosis, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Health Care Crisis, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Health Care Information System (HCIS), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Health Care Issues, General, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Health Care, National, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Health Care Personnel: Work Group Report, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Health Care Reform: Articles from Public Employee Press, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Health Care Reform Rally (Washington DC), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Hill, Stanley, 1982-1992 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Hill, Stanley: Letter to Dennis Rivera (re: Carrillo), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Hill v. Giuliani (Tax Levy), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month (L-420), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Home Care Workers Rally, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Homeless: Giuliani Plan, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Hormel Strike, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Hospital Closings: Butler Testimony, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Hospital Overcrowding: Article List, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Hospital Workers, General: Public Employee Press Article, Undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Housing, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Hughes, Charles, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Immigration Law, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association (NY Chapter), Aug 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Infectious Waste, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Infectious Waste: "Red Bag", 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Infectious Waste: Safety Conference, Sep 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Institutional Aides: Corrections, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Institutional Services Unit: Agreement, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - International Association of Healthcare Central Service Material Management, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - ILGWU: Domsey Strike, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - International Socialist Organization, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - IV Technicians, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - IV Technicians: Unlicensed, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Israel: Histadrut, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Jackson Democratic Club: Robeson Award, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Jackson, Jesse: Campaign, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Jamaica: Disaster Relief, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Currents, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Job Freeze/Budget Cuts, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Job Titles (Broad-banding), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Jobs with Peace Resolution, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Joint Labor-Management Committee on Child Care, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Jones, Thomas Russell (Judge), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Kauvar, Abraham: Protest and Resignation, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Kauvar, Abraham: Replacement Committee, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Keep the Dream Alive, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - King Emmanuel Baptist Church, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Birthday Celebration (Atlanta), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr. Day: Hearing on Venice, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Holiday, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Institute, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Memorials (Memphis, TN), 1987, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - King's County Hospital, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - King's County Hospital, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - King's County Hospital: Crisis, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - King's County Hospital: Downstate Medical Center, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - King's County Hospital: Fight Incident, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - King's County Hospital: Health and Safety, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - King's County Hospital: IV Team, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - King's County Hospital: Plan of Correction, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - King's County Hospital: Turkey Raffle, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - King's County Hospital/University Hospital, 1991-1997 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - King's County Hospital: University Hospital: Elections, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - King's County Hospital: University Hospital: Lash Group Study, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - King's County Hospital: Waste Management, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Koch, Edward, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Labor Advisory Board Meeting, Mar 1991 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Labor Committee for Chile, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Labor Committee on Social/Economic Justice: Albany, NY, Mar 1991 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA), 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - LCLAA: Conference (Puerto Rico), 1990-1997 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Labor Day Parade, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Labor Mass, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Labor Research Association: William Lucy, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Labor Solidarity Breakfast, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Labor's Voices Conference, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Laundries, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Layoffs, 1991-1999 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Layoffs: Preferred Lists, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Legislation, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Legislation: Pensions, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Licensed Practical Nurse Program, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Lincoln Hospital, 1985-1992 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Accreditation, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Lincoln Hospital: AIDS Unit, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Lincoln Hospital: B. Thomas Study of Problems, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Carlos Molina, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln Hospital: CCU, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Crisis, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Crisis, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Demonstration, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Flow Sheets (Nurses Aides), 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Health and Safety, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Housekeeping Department, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Information on AIDS, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lincoln Hospital: IV Teams, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Layoffs, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Meetings, 1988-2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Nurse Aides, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Personnel, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Problems, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Protests, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Quinones Resignation, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Red Bags, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Thelma Richards' Death, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lobby Days, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Lobbying (Albany), 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Lobbying Institute, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Local 1199: Doris Turner, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Local 1199: Hospital Workers Union, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Local 1199/Local 1115 Merger, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Locus, Johnnie, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Long-Term Care, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Lucy, William, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Lump Sum Payments, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Mandela, Nelson, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Manhattan House of Detention, 1989-1995 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - March for Peace and Justice in Central America (Washington, DC), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - March for Racial Justice, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - March on Washington, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Mayoral Forum on health Care, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Mayor's Financial Plan, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - McDonald's Protest, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Medicaid Cutback Rally, Albany, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Medicaid Managed Care Plan, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Medical Arts Center Hospital, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Medical Disability (Members), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Medical Surgical Technicians, 1982, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Membership Figures, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Membership Meetings, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Memos (L-420), 2000 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Mental Health Assistant Course, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Metropolitan Hospital, 1982-1999 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: Cafeteria Privatization, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: IV Team, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: Labor-Management, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: Layoffs, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: Nurse Aides, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Metropolitan Lumber, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Military Nursing Program Meeting, Dec 21, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Minter, Thomas: for Schools Chancellor, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1986-1998 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Mitchell, Rachel-Jean: Scholarship Fund, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - M.L. Wilson Boys Club of Harlem, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Montefiore Medical Center, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Morrisania Center, 1990-2001 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Mortuary Technicians, Undated, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Municipal Coalition: Agreement, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Municipal Credit Election, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1990-1991, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - National Agenda for Economic Justice, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 66)